abliker.com 2018-07-10

# Privacy Policy - AbLiker

* * *

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support at abliker.com. At AbLiker we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by AbLiker and how we use it. 

* * *

#### We Don't Share your Accesstoken & Personal Information

> Your access_token is Secured & will never be shared with any other Autoliker in any case. Your Access Token and Personal Information is Secured and we Never Shared it with Others. 

#### We Use Cookies

> AbLiker uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

#### We use Third party websites for ADS

> We use Online ADS on our Website to Run Because the Revenue come from ADS Network is helped us to run Our Server and Give our User a NON-STOP Service, you can Support us by Clicking ADS on our Website. 

#### Our privacy policy Changes

> We Recommend to our Users to check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. 

#### Your acceptance to our Privacy Policy

> By using ABLIKER you are ACCEPTING our Terms & Policies, we store your Access Token to exchange Likes & comments with other users of AbLiker. Please read our Terms & Policies to Learn More. 

_This document was Last Edited on: 10-26-2016_
